Guide to the Beer Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- THOMAS BEER, 1897-1947; Series III; 12.7' (32 boxes)
  - Published Writings
    - Short Stories
      - "Voices", 1936 April 16 (Box 109, Folder 222)
      - "Men Never Understand Their Sons", 1947 (Box 109, Folder 223)
      - "Succor", 1947 (Box 109, Folder 224)
      - "The Winter Calf", 1947 (Box 109, Folder 225)
      - Reviews of short stories, 1918-1947 (Box 109, Folder 226)
    - Articles and Book Reviews
      - "The Glass Bell", 1910 May (Box 109, Folder 227)
      - "Othello's Occupation", 1911 January (Box 109, Folder 228)
      - "The Harmless Sport", 1921 July 30 (Box 109, Folder 229)
      - "Notes on the American Gentlewoman", 1921 November (Box 109, Folder 230)
      - "The Mauve Decade", 1922 February (Box 109, Folder 231)
      - "For Muted Strings", 1922 July (Box 109, Folder 232)
      - "The Nietzschean Follies VII: Young Muckers", 1922 August (Box 109, Folder 233)
      - "Six Islanders.", 1923 October 6 (Box 109, Folder 234)
        See also: box 94, folder 14
      - "Frank Swinnerton", 1923 December (Box 109, Folder 235)
      - "Civilized Thought", 1924 September 13 (Box 109, Folder 236)
      - "Richard Harding Davis", 1924 October (Box 109, Folder 237)
      - "Screaming Eagles", 1925 February (Box 109, Folder 238)
      - "The Princess Far Away", 1925 April 25 (Box 109, Folder 239)
      - "Fire Feathers", 1925 December 19 (Box 109, Folder 240)
      - "Miss Cather", 1925 (Box 109, Folder 241)
      - "Hypocrisy", 1927 January (Box 109, Folder 242)
      - "An Irritating Archangel", 1927 December (Box 109, Folder 243)
      - "Introduction," George W. Bellows: His Lithographs. Reviews, 1927 (Box 109, Folder 244)
      - "Ten Years After", 1928 (Box 109, Folder 245)
      - "Towards Sunrise, 1920-1930", 1930 May (Box 109, Folder 246)
      - "A Little Exam", 1931 January (Box 109, Folder 247)
      - "Bud on Nantucket Island", 1932 January (Box 109, Folder 248)
      - "Menu", 1932 December (Box 109, Folder 249)
      - "Death at 5:45 P. M.", 1933 February (Box 109, Folder 250)
      - "Mrs. Stephen Crane", 1934 March (Box 109, Folder 251)
      - "Go Dine Your Enemy", 1934 April (Box 110, Folder 252)
      - "Nonsense, Renewed", 1934 May (Box 110, Folder 253)
      - "Current Mysteries", 1934 June (Box 110, Folder 254)
      - "Playboy", 1934 June (Box 110, Folder 255)
      - "Edmund", 1934 July (Box 110, Folder 256)
      - "Conduct of a Grandfather", 1934 November (Box 110, Folder 257)
      - "Written on Friday", 1935 March (Box 110, Folder 258)
      - "Against Memory", 1936 February (Box 110, Folder 259)
      - Book reviews, 1910-1935 (Box 110, Folder 260)
    - Poems
      - "The Last Ballade", 1907 December (Box 110, Folder 261)
      - "Delilah", 1908 June (Box 110, Folder 262)
      - "Exit", 1908 December (Box 110, Folder 263)
      - "Slaves in Babylon, 1909 November (Box 110, Folder 264)
      - "Dirge for Rudel", 1909 December (Box 110, Folder 265)
      - "The New School.", 1910 January
        See: box 107, folder 168
      - Yale Class Poem, 1911 June 20 (Box 110, Folder 266)
    - Letters from Readers
      - The Fair Rewards, 1922-1938 (Box 111, Folder 267)
      - Stephen Crane, 1923-1940 (Box 111, Folder 268)
      - Sandoval, 1924 (Box 111, Folder 269)
      - The Mauve Decade, 1926-1940 (Box 111, Folder 270)
      - The Road to Heaven, 1929-1931 (Box 111, Folder 271)
      - Hanna, 1929-1940 (Box 111, Folder 272)
      - Army stories, 1926-1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 273)
      - Van Eck stories, 1927-1938, undated (Box 111, Folder 274)
      - General, 1911-1940, undated (Box 111, Folder 275-282)
      - Manuscripts submitted by readers, 1935, undated (Box 111, Folder 283)
  - Unpublished Writings
    - Books
      - Contented Charles. Holograph drafts (Box 112, Folder 284-285)
      - Contented Charles. Typescript drafts (Box 112, Folder 286-287)
      - The Country of the Young. Holograph fragments (Box 112, Folder 288)
      - The Country of the Young. Holograph fragments (Box 112, Folder 289)
      - The Country of the Young. Holograph and typescript fragments in sequence with notes by Alice Beer (Box 112, Folder 290)
      - The Country of the Young. Type-script fragments with notes by Alice Beer (Box 112, Folder 291)
      - The Country of the Young. Chapter I, 14 pp. typescript. (Box 112, Folder 292)
      - The Country of the Young. Chapters typescript (Box 112, Folder 293)
      - The Country of the Young. Chapters I-VI, 98 pp. typescript carbon (Box 113, Folder 294)
      - Form Color and Desire. Notes (Box 113, Folder 295)
      - Form Color and Desire. Outline and Chapter I in typescript (Box 113, Folder 296)
      - Noel Farquhar. Holograph drafts (Box 113, Folder 297-300)
      - Noel Farquhar. Holograph draft (Box 113, Folder 301-302)
      - Noel Farquhar. Typescript pages (Box 113, Folder 303)
      - Noel Farquhar. Typescript draft (Box 114, Folder 304)
      - Sunlight. Holograph and typescript fragments, [ca. 1918?] (Box 114, Folder 305)
      - Collected short stories of Stephen Crane. Table of contents and introduction. Drafts. (Box 114, Folder 306)
      - Untitled novel about Gavin Kent. Incomplete holograph draft (Box 114, Folder 307-308)
      - Untitled novel set in Zerbetta, about Jerome Beyle, Andrew Korn and Jim Coe. Holograph and typescript fragments (Box 114, Folder 309)
      - Untitled novel set in Zerbetta and in New York, about Angus Kerr. Incomplete holograph draft (Box 114, Folder 310-312)
      - Untitled novel set in Zerbetta, about Angus Kerr. Typescript fragment (Box 115, Folder 313)
    - Short Stories
      - Bibliography of unpublished stories. Catalogue and synopses by Alice Beer. (Box 115, Folder 314)
      - "Abbot Plurimus." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 315)
      - "About Emotional Disturbances." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 316)
      - "Account Stated." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 317)
      - "Barbary." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 318)
      - "Barcarolle." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 319)
      - "The Button Moulder." Complete, [ca. 1907-1911?] (Box 115, Folder 320)
      - "Carmelsville High." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 321)
      - "The Chameleon." Complete, [1919?] (Box 115, Folder 322)
      - "Circe and Mr. Lent." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 323)
      - "Cora Darling." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 324)
      - "The Dark Closet." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 325)
      - "Decennial." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 326)
      - "Deirdre." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 327)
      - "Edwina." Complete, [ca. 1912?] (Box 115, Folder 328)
      - "An Emblem." Complete, [ca. 1917?] (Box 115, Folder 329)
      - "An Epilogue to Faust." Complete, [ca. 1907-1l?] (Box 115, Folder 330)
      - "Feudalists." Complete, [ca. 1907-1910?]. (Box 115, Folder 331)
      - "The Flight." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 332)
      - "The Gentle Soul." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 333)
      - "Heliomaenes." Complete, [ca. 1907-1911?] (Box 115, Folder 334)
      - "High Strategy." Complete, [ca. 1918?] (Box 115, Folder 335)
      - "The Holy Estate." Complete, [ca. 1916] (Box 115, Folder 336)
      - "Home Is the Sailor." Complete, undated (Box 115, Folder 337)
      - "Humble Pup." Complete, [ca. 1936?] (Box 115, Folder 338)
      - "Ilium, Ohio." Incomplete, [1939?] (Box 115, Folder 339)
      - "In the Day of Success." Incomplete, undated (Box 115, Folder 340)
      - "It Does, Sometimes." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 341)
      - "Jove." Complete, undated (Box 116, Folder 342)
      - "Luscious Moment" or "Humble Pup" or "Humble Hounds." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 343)
      - "Luscious Moment" or "Humble Pup" or "Humble Hounds." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 344)
      - "Luscious Moment" or "Humble Pup" or "Humble Hounds." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 345)
      - "The Other Narcissus." Complete., undated (Box 116, Folder 346)
        See also: box 108A, folder 190
      - "Pharoah's Daughter." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 347)
      - "The Protestant." Complete, [ca. 1917] (Box 116, Folder 348)
      - "Red Horses." Complete, undated (Box 116, Folder 349)
      - "Red Sabbath," Complete, undated (Box 116, Folder 350)
      - "The Relay." Complete, undated (Box 116, Folder 351)
      - "Samarcand." Complete, Circa 1935 (Box 116, Folder 352)
      - "A Simple Arcadian Tale." Complete, undated (Box 116, Folder 353)
      - "Sophistication." Incomplete Ms. transferred to Published Writings, undated (Box 116, Folder 354)
      - "Style." Incomplete, undated (Box 116, Folder 355)
      - "To Cytherea." Complete, [ca. 1907-1910?]. (Box 116, Folder 356)
      - "The Wall of Questions." Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 357)
      - "Wednesday Comes Right After Tuesday." Complete, [1932?] (Box 117, Folder 358)
      - "When It Did Happen." Complete, [1935?] (Box 117, Folder 359)
      - "World's Poison." Incomplete, [ca. 1928?] (Box 117, Folder 360)
      - "Worse Than the Chair." Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 361)
      - Untitled ghost story. Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 362)
      - Untitled mystery set at Lake Superior. Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 363)
      - Untitled story about a minister who wanted to be a prize fighter. Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 364)
      - Untitled story about a retired actress who returns to the stage. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 365)
      - Untitled story about Minor Braden. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 366)
      - Untitled stories about Abdul Hirsch. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 367)
      - Untitled stories about Stukely Kent and Joe Fancher. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 368)
      - Untitled story about Jesse King. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 369)
      - Untitled story about Patrick Kinney, a prizefighter. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 370)
      - Untitled story set at Lake Tahoe. Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 371)
      - Untitled story set in Edwardsville, Ohio, circa 1917. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 372)
      - Untitled story set in a Seattle logging camp. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 373)
      - Untitled Zerbetta story about Bud Andrews, undated (Box 117, Folder 374)
      - Untitled Zerbetta stories about Calvin Bayliss. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 375)
      - Untitled Zerbetta story about Jerome Palliser. Complete, undated (Box 117, Folder 376)
      - Untitled Zerbetta story about Jordan Sims, undated (Box 117, Folder 377)
      - Untitled Zerbetta story. Incomplete, undated (Box 117, Folder 378)
      - Fragments, undated (Box 117, Folder 379)
      - Fragments, undated (Box 118, Folder 380-381)
    - Articles and Book Reyiews
      - "The Broomes", undated (Box 118, Folder 382)
      - "Enlisted Man", undated (Box 118, Folder 383)
      - "Europe in Danger; A Diatribe", undated (Box 118, Folder 384)
      - "The Useful Man", undated (Box 118, Folder 385)
      - "Witness for the Heathen", undated (Box 118, Folder 386)
      - "Writers and Memory." Incomplete, undated (Box 118, Folder 387)
      - Fragments, undated (Box 118, Folder 388)
    - Plays and Movie Scenarios
      - Bread and Butter, undated (Box 118, Folder 389)
      - The Dark Edge, undated (Box 118, Folder 390)
      - Deep Water, undated (Box 118, Folder 391)
      - The Devil's Child, undated (Box 118, Folder 392)
      - The Good Little Town, [1921?] (Box 118, Folder 393)
      - Happy Land. Incomplete drafts, undated (Box 118, Folder 394)
      - In Freedom's Name. by Thomas Beer and John Peter Toohey. Drafts, 1922 (Box 118, Folder 395)
      - In Freedom's Name. Typescript, 1922 (Box 118, Folder 396)
      - Jim by Thomas Beer and Edgar M. Woolley. Drafts (Box 118, Folder 397)
      - Jim Typescript, undated (Box 118, Folder 398)
      - Jim Typescript carbon, undated (Box 119, Folder 399)
      - Men Call It Love, undated (Box 119, Folder 400)
      - Mortimer. Incomplete draft, undated (Box 119, Folder 401)
      - One Hundred Years Ago, undated (Box 119, Folder 402)
      - The Plot Thickens. Adaptation of Quello Che Non T'Aspetti by Luigi Barzini and Arnaldo Fraccaroli. Incomplete, [1922?] (Box 119, Folder 403)
      - The Plot Thickens. Reviews (Box 119, Folder 404)
      - The Sheet. Typescript, undated (Box 119, Folder 405)
      - Somethin' Queer, undated (Box 119, Folder 406)
      - The Sun Dance, undated (Box 119, Folder 407)
      - 39-East. Typescript of act III, undated (Box 119, Folder 408)
      - Untitled play about the emperor Valentinian, undated (Box 119, Folder 409)
      - Fragments, undated (Box 119, Folder 410)
    - Juvenilia
      - compositions and short stories, undated (Box 119, Folder 411)
      - plays, undated (Box 124, Folder 412)
      - poems, 1903-1911, undated (Box 124, Folder 413)
  - Personal Files
    - address book (Box 120, Folder 414)
    - catalog of Thomas Beer's art library, undated (Box 120, Folder 415)
    - certificates, 1902-1918 (Box 120, Folder 416)
    - drawings, undated (Box 120, Folder 417)
    - education: J. M. Mason School and Mackenzie School; exercises and examinations, 1897-1906 (Box 120, Folder 418)
    - education; Mackenzie School; note-books, undated (Box 120, Folder 419)
    - education; Mackenzie School; Town and Gown, Thomas Beer, editor, 1905-1907 (Box 120, Folder 420)
    - education; Mackenzie School: yearbook, 1904 (Box 120, Folder 421)
    - education; Mackenzie School; memorabilia, 1906, undated (Box 120, Folder 422)
    - education; Yale College; course schedules, 1907-1911 (Box 120, Folder 423)
    - education; Yale College; English themes, 1910-1911 (Box 121, Folder 424)
    - education: Yale College; French history notebook, 1911 (Box 121, Folder 425)
    - education; Yale College; literature notebook, 1911 (Box 121, Folder 426)
    - education: Yale College: examinations, notes, 1905-1911 (Box 121, Folder 427)
    - education: Yale College; Commencement, 1911 (Box 121, Folder 428)
    - education: Yale College: memorabilia, 1907-1911 (Box 121, Folder 429)
    - education: Yale College: theatrical memorabilia, 1911, undated (Box 121, Folder 430)
    - education: Yale College: theatrical memorabilia, undated (Box 121, Folder 431)
    - education: Columbia University: course selections and grades, 1912, undated (Box 122, Folder 432)
    - education: Columbia University; examinations, 1910, undated (Box 122, Folder 433)
    - education: Columbia University; law notebooks, 1910-1914, undated (Box 122, Folder 434-439)
    - education; Columbia University; Lawyers Commonplace Book, undated (Box 122, Folder 440)
    - education; Law clerkship, 1911 (Box 122, Folder 441)
    - juvenilia; art work, undated (Box 123, Folder 442)
    - juvenilia: memorabilia, undated (Box 123, Folder 443)
    - memorabilia: book plates, calling cards, stationery, undated (Box 123, Folder 444)
    - memorabilia: European trips, 1928, undated (Box 123, Folder 445-446)
    - memorabilia: newspapers and miscellaneous printed material, 1922-1931 (Box 123, Folder 447)
    - memorabilia: photographs, undated (Box 123, Folder 448)
    - memorabilia: theater notebook, Circa 1910 (Box 123, Folder 449)
    - memorabilia: theater programs, 1918, undated (Box 123, Folder 450)
    - memorabilia: U.S. Army, 1918-1919 (Box 124, Folder 451)
    - mental health. (Box 124, Folder 451)
      See also: box 127, folder 75a
    - passports (Box 124, Folder 452)
    - pocket diaries, 1922, 1927, undated (Box 124, Folder 453)
    - biographical information; autobiographical notes, 1922, 1926 (Box 124, Folder 454)
    - biographical information; obituaries, 1940 (Box 124, Folder 455)
    - biographical information; reminiscences of Thomas Beer by family and friends, undated (Box 124, Folder 456)
- ALICE BALDWIN BEER, 1896-1969; Series IV; 8.5' (21 boxes)
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by writer. Letters written by Alice Baldwin Beer are filed under the name of the addressee. General correspondence concerning the financial and legal affairs of Thomas Beer is filed at the end of the section.
  The material in Antique Textiles Businessis arranged under the following categories: Correspondence with Clients and Dealers (alphabetically by name of correspondent or topic); Financial Records (alphabetically by topic); Stock Inventories (alphabetically by topic); Reference Material (alphabetically by topic); and Personal Files is arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1945-1953 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Abbott, Cary, 1928, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 2)
      To/From: 3/4
    - B, 1910-1946 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Bacon, Leonard, 1941 (Box 125, Folder 4)
      To/From: 2/1
    - Beer, William, 1910-1917 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1940-1942 (Box 125, Folder 6)
      To/From: 0/2
    - Berryman, John, 1948 (Box 125, Folder 7)
      To/From: 3/5
    - Bowers, Claude G., 1939 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Boyd, Ernest, 1940 (Box 125, Folder 9)
      To/From: 1/1
    - Burlingame, C. C., 1941-1942 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Byne, Mildred Stapley., 1931-1936 (Box 125, Folder 11)
      To/From: 18/3
      See also: box 128-134, folder 81-163
    - Byne, Mildred Stapley, 1937-1941 (Box 125, Folder 12)
      To/From: 16/3
    - C-D, 1901-1961 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Cabell, James Branch and Margaret, 1947-1961 (Box 125, Folder 14)
      To/From: 1-5/3
    - Collings, Patricia, 1944 (Box 125, Folder 15)
      To/From: 0/1
    - Crane, Edith, 1948-1955 (Box 125, Folder 16)
      To/From: 13/8
    - Crane, Edith, 1956-1960 (Box 125, Folder 17)
      To/From: 12/9
    - Crawford, John Douglas, 1909-1910 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Crowley, Alice Lewisohn., 1936, undated (Box 125, Folder 19)
      See also: box 127, folder 54
    - DeOnis, Federico, 1936-1940 (Box 125, Folder 20)
      To/From: 9112
    - De Ternova, Rose (Lehman), 1938-1940 (Box 125, Folder 21)
      To/From: 12/6
    - E-F, 1916-1960 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Fair, James. H.S. and Mary, 1908-1910, undated (Box 125, Folder 23)
      To/From: 28-1/0
    - Fisher, Harold H., 1916-1918 (Box 125, Folder 24)
      To/From: 10/0
    - Fisher, Harold H., 1938-1959 (Box 125, Folder 25)
      To/From: 11/3
    - Fisher, Helen Dwight, 1916-1941 (Box 125, Folder 26)
      To/From: 21/0
    - Fisher, Helen Dwight, 1942-1961 (Box 125, Folder 27)
      To/From: 13/3
    - Follett, Wilson, 1947-1955 (Box 126, Folder 28)
    - G, 1919-1958 (Box 126, Folder 29)
    - Gailor, Charlotte, 1916-1919 (Box 126, Folder 30)
    - Garfunkel, George, 1940-1959 (Box 126, Folder 31)
      To/From: 13/21
    - Gilkes, Lillian B., 1956-1959 (Box 126, Folder 32)
      To/From: 7/5
    - Gray, Beryl Evans (Mrs. Mason), 1908-1910 (Box 126, Folder 33)
    - Gray, Beryl Evans (Mrs. Mason), 1913-1915 (Box 126, Folder 34)
      To/From: 16/0
    - Gray, Elmore B., 1909-1910 (Box 126, Folder 35)
    - H, 1929-1961 (Box 126, Folder 36)
    - Housum, Robert., 1917-1919, 1937-1948, 1961 (Box 126, Folder 37)
      See also: box 127, folder 75
    - I-J-K-L, 1916-1961 (Box 126, Folder 38)
    - Jones, Edith Richie, 1948 (Box 126, Folder 39)
      To/From: 2/2
    - Keller, Morton, 1957-1960 (Box 126, Folder 40)
      To/From: 3/2
    - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche W.; Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1937-1940 (Box 126, Folder 41)
      To/From: 14-3/5
    - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche W.; Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 126, Folder 42)
      To/From: 12-3/13
    - Knopf, Alfred A, and Blanche W.; Alfred A, Knopf, Inc., 1943-1949 (Box 126, Folder 43)
      To/From: 22-0/20
    - Knopf, Alfred A. and Blanche W.; Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1950-1965 (Box 126, Folder 44)
      To/From: 6-0/4
    - Lawrence, Frederic M., 1948 (Box 126, Folder 45)
      To/From: 1/2
      See also: box 39-42, folder 439-469 See also: box 100, folder 91
    - Lewisohn, Alice. (Box 126, Folder 45)
      see: box 125, folder 19
    - Lewisohn, Irene., 1922-1936 (Box 126, Folder 46)
      To/From: 23/1
      The Neighborhood Playhouse and Antique Textiles Business, Correspondence with Clients and Dealers
    - Lombardi, Cornelius, 1909-1910 (Box 126, Folder 47)
    - M-N, 1912-1950 (Box 126, Folder 48)
    - Minnegerode, Meade, 1911-1917 (Box 127, Folder 49)
      To/From: 37/0
    - Minnegerode, Meade, 1918 (Box 127, Folder 50)
      To/From: 19/0
    - Minnegerode, Meade, 1919-1923, 1939-1957 (Box 127, Folder 51)
    - Mumford, Lewis, 1937-1943, 1965 (Box 127, Folder 52)
      To/From: 9/2
    - Munoz, Inès, 1936, undated (Box 127, Folder 53)
    - Neighborhood Playhouse, The., 1919-1923, undated (Box 127, Folder 54)
      See also: box 125, folder 19 See also: box 130, folder 109
    - New York School of Interior Decoration, The, 1937-1941 (Box 127, Folder 55)
    - Nowell, Elizabeth, 1950 (Box 127, Folder 56)
      To/From: 3/1
    - O-P-Q, 1919-1960, undated (Box 127, Folder 57)
    - Ober, Harold, 1937-1941 (Box 127, Folder 58)
      To/From: 3/6
    - Palmer, Margaret., 1931-1951 (Box 127, Folder 59)
      To/From: 11/4
      See also: box 125, folder 19 See also: box 125, folder 25
    - R-S, 1896-1969 (Box 127, Folder 60)
    - Roach, Mariana, 1940-1942 (Box 127, Folder 61)
    - Schoberlin, Melvin H., 1948-1956 (Box 127, Folder 62)
      To/From: 6/8
    - Stallman, R. W., 1956-1957 (Box 127, Folder 63)
      To/From: 8/3
    - T-U-V, 1916-1930 (Box 127, Folder 64)
    - Tilghman, J. Donnell, 1937-1959 (Box 127, Folder 65)
      To/From: 22/2
    - Tuttle, Emerson and Isabelle (Hollister)., 1940-1946 (Box 127, Folder 66)
      To/From: 3-1/1
    - W-X-Y-Z, 1901-1958 (Box 127, Folder 67)
    - War Camp Community Service., 1918-1919 (Box 127, Folder 68)
      See also: box 144, folder 255
    - Weissberger, Herbert P., 1959 (Box 127, Folder 69)
    - Weissberger, José A., 1934-1945, undated (Box 127, Folder 70)
      To/From: 25/9
    - Wilkins, Frederic and Helen, 1935-1939, undated (Box 127, Folder 71)
      To/From: 2-4/1
    - Williams, Jesse Lynch, undated (Box 127, Folder 72)
    - Woolley, Edgar Montillion., 1905-1906, 1940-1954, undated (Box 127, Folder 73)
      To/From: 10/3
      See also: box 127, folder 75 See also: box 127, folder 75
    - correspondence re: hospitalization of Thomas Beer, 1937-1940 (Box 127, Folder 74)
    - correspondence re; Financial aid for hospitalization of Thomas Beer, 1937-1938 (Box 127, Folder 75)
    - correspondence re: mental health of Thomas Beer, 1939 (Box 127, Folder 75a)
    - correspondence in response to a request for biographical data about Thomas Beer, 1940 (Box 127, Folder 76)
    - correspondence re: motion picture and dramatic rights for works of Thomas Beer, 1941-1945 (Box 128, Folder 77)
    - correspondence re: subsidiary rights for publication of the works of Thomas Beer in anthologies and in translation, 1945-1961 (Box 128, Folder 78)
    - correspondence re: television rights for works of Thomas Beer, 1956-1957 (Box 128, Folder 79)
    - unidentified, 1928-1947, undated (Box 128, Folder 80)
  - Antique Textiles Business
    - Correspondence with Clients and Dealers
      - A-C, 1932-1944 (Box 128, Folder 81)
      - D-F, 1937-1944 (Box 128, Folder 82)
      - G-L, 1936-1944 (Box 128, Folder 83)
      - M-N-, 1936-1941 (Box 128, Folder 84)
      - O-S, 1932-1943 (Box 128, Folder 85)
      - T, 1937-1943 (Box 128, Folder 86)
      - U-Z, 1941-1944 (Box 128, Folder 87)
      - Ashley, Edgar, 1932-1934 (Box 128, Folder 88)
      - Brix, Mrs. Maurice, 1939-1944 (Box 129, Folder 89)
      - Byne, Arthur and Mildred Stapley, 1929-1940 (Box 129, Folder 90-91)
      - Byne textiles; correspondence, 1934-1940 (Box 129, Folder 92)
      - Byne textiles: invoices, 1928-1937 (Box 129, Folder 93)
      - Cordley, Julia D., 1939-1940 (Box 129, Folder 94)